[
    {
        "question": "What was the assets current assets cash and cash equivalents in 2023?",
        "answer": "For the year 2023, the assets current assets cash and cash equivalents was $1,481 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the current investments trade receivables in 2023?",
        "answer": "For the year 2023, the current investments trade receivables was $3,094 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unbilled revenues in 2023?",
        "answer": "For the year 2023, the unbilled revenues was $1,861 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the prepayments and other current assets in 2023?",
        "answer": "For the year 2023, the prepayments and other current assets was $1,336 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the income tax assets derivative financial instruments total current assets in 2023?",
        "answer": "For the year 2023, the income tax assets derivative financial instruments total current assets was $8,626 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the non-current assets property, plant and equipment in 2023?",
        "answer": "For the year 2023, the non-current assets property, plant and equipment was $1,679 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the right-of-use assets goodwill intangible assets non-current investments in 2023?",
        "answer": "For the year 2023, the right-of-use assets goodwill intangible assets non-current investments was $1,530 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unbilled revenues deferred income tax assets income tax assets other non-current assets total non-current assets in 2023?",
        "answer": "For the year 2023, the unbilled revenues deferred income tax assets income tax assets other non-current assets total non-current assets was $6,686 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total assets in 2023?",
        "answer": "For the year 2023, the total assets was $15,312 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the liabilities and equity current liabilities trade payables lease liabilities derivative financial instruments current income tax liabilities unearned revenues employee benefit obligations provisions other current liabilities in 2023?",
        "answer": "For the year 2023, the liabilities and equity current liabilities trade payables lease liabilities derivative financial instruments current income tax liabilities unearned revenues employee benefit obligations provisions other current liabilities was $2,403 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total current liabilities in 2023?",
        "answer": "For the year 2023, the total current liabilities was $4,769 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the non-current liabilities lease liabilities deferred income tax liabilities employee benefit obligations other non-current liabilities total liabilities in 2023?",
        "answer": "For the year 2023, the non-current liabilities lease liabilities deferred income tax liabilities employee benefit obligations other non-current liabilities total liabilities was $6,088 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the equity share capital   ($0.16) par value in 2023?",
        "answer": "For the year 2023, the equity share capital   ($0.16) par value was $4,800,000,000 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the authorized equity shares, issued and outstanding in 2023?",
        "answer": "For the year 2023, the authorized equity shares, issued and outstanding was $4,136,387,925 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the equity shares fully paid up, net of in 2023?",
        "answer": "For the year 2023, the equity shares fully paid up, net of was $12,172,119 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the treasury shares each as of march in 2023?",
        "answer": "For the year 2023, the treasury shares each as of march was $31, million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the (march in 2023?",
        "answer": "For the year 2023, the (march was $31, million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the ), respectively share premium retained earnings in 2023?",
        "answer": "For the year 2023, the ), respectively share premium retained earnings was $11,401 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the cash flow hedge reserve  other reserves in 2023?",
        "answer": "For the year 2023, the cash flow hedge reserve  other reserves was $1,370 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the capital redemption reserve other components of equity in 2023?",
        "answer": "For the year 2023, the capital redemption reserve other components of equity was $(4,314) million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total equity attributable to equity holders of the company in 2023?",
        "answer": "For the year 2023, the total equity attributable to equity holders of the company was $9,172 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the non-controlling interests total equity in 2023?",
        "answer": "For the year 2023, the non-controlling interests total equity was $9,224 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the assets current assets cash and cash equivalents in 2024?",
        "answer": "For the year 2024, the assets current assets cash and cash equivalents was $1,773 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the current investments 1,548 trade receivables in 2024?",
        "answer": "For the year 2024, the current investments 1,548 trade receivables was $3,620 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unbilled revenues in 2024?",
        "answer": "For the year 2024, the unbilled revenues was $1,531 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the prepayments and other current assets in 2024?",
        "answer": "For the year 2024, the prepayments and other current assets was $1,473 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the income tax assets derivative financial instruments total current assets in 2024?",
        "answer": "For the year 2024, the income tax assets derivative financial instruments total current assets was $10,722 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the non-current assets property, plant and equipment in 2024?",
        "answer": "For the year 2024, the non-current assets property, plant and equipment was $1,537 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the right-of-use assets goodwill intangible assets non-current investments in 2024?",
        "answer": "For the year 2024, the right-of-use assets goodwill intangible assets non-current investments was $1,404 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unbilled revenues deferred income tax assets income tax assets other non-current assets total non-current assets in 2024?",
        "answer": "For the year 2024, the unbilled revenues deferred income tax assets income tax assets other non-current assets total non-current assets was $5,801 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total assets in 2024?",
        "answer": "For the year 2024, the total assets was $16,523 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the liabilities and equity current liabilities trade payables lease liabilities derivative financial instruments current income tax liabilities unearned revenues employee benefit obligations provisions other current liabilities in 2024?",
        "answer": "For the year 2024, the liabilities and equity current liabilities trade payables lease liabilities derivative financial instruments current income tax liabilities unearned revenues employee benefit obligations provisions other current liabilities was $2,099 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total current liabilities in 2024?",
        "answer": "For the year 2024, the total current liabilities was $4,651 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the non-current liabilities lease liabilities deferred income tax liabilities employee benefit obligations other non-current liabilities total liabilities in 2024?",
        "answer": "For the year 2024, the non-current liabilities lease liabilities deferred income tax liabilities employee benefit obligations other non-current liabilities total liabilities was $5,918 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the equity share capital   ($0.16) par value in 2024?",
        "answer": "For the year 2024, the equity share capital   ($0.16) par value was $4,800,000,000 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the authorized equity shares, issued and outstanding in 2024?",
        "answer": "For the year 2024, the authorized equity shares, issued and outstanding was $4,139,950,635 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the equity shares fully paid up, net of in 2024?",
        "answer": "For the year 2024, the equity shares fully paid up, net of was $10,916,829 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the treasury shares each as of march in 2024?",
        "answer": "For the year 2024, the treasury shares each as of march was $31, million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the (march in 2024?",
        "answer": "For the year 2024, the (march was $31, million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the ), respectively share premium retained earnings in 2024?",
        "answer": "For the year 2024, the ), respectively share premium retained earnings was $12,557 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the cash flow hedge reserve  other reserves in 2024?",
        "answer": "For the year 2024, the cash flow hedge reserve  other reserves was $1,623 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the capital redemption reserve other components of equity in 2024?",
        "answer": "For the year 2024, the capital redemption reserve other components of equity was $(4,396) million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total equity attributable to equity holders of the company in 2024?",
        "answer": "For the year 2024, the total equity attributable to equity holders of the company was $10,559 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the non-controlling interests total equity in 2024?",
        "answer": "For the year 2024, the non-controlling interests total equity was $10,605 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the revenues in 2023?",
        "answer": "For the year 2023, the revenues was $18,212 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the 13,561 cost of sales in 2023?",
        "answer": "For the year 2023, the 13,561 cost of sales was $12,709 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the 8,828 gross profit in 2023?",
        "answer": "For the year 2023, the 8,828 gross profit was $5,503 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the 4,733 operating expenses: selling and marketing expenses administrative expenses total operating expenses in 2023?",
        "answer": "For the year 2023, the 4,733 operating expenses: selling and marketing expenses administrative expenses total operating expenses was $1,678 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the 1,408 operating profit in 2023?",
        "answer": "For the year 2023, the 1,408 operating profit was $3,825 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the 3,325 other income, net finance cost profit before income taxes in 2023?",
        "answer": "For the year 2023, the 3,325 other income, net finance cost profit before income taxes was $4,125 million."
    }
]